

PERSONAL

Birthday : 6th June 1995
Relationship : Married
Nationality : Russian

Languages : English, Russian, Turkish

SKILLS

C#

JAVA

PYTHON

SQL

ASP.NET CORE 3

SOFTWARE

OPENGL

PHOTOSHOP ILLUSTRATOR 3DS MAX MS OFFICE HTML 5 CSS

CONTACT



+90 541 979 08 27



nastasia bayraktar@gmail.com



nastasiabayraktar.github.io/NB



Sakarya / Serdivan

ANASTASIA BAYRAKTAR

Computer Engineering Student

PROFILE

I'M ANASTASİA

I am a hardworking and ambitious individual with a great passion for the IT industry. I am currently studying Computer Engineering at Sakarya University. I have excellent communication skills, enabling me to effectively communicate with a wide range of people. I am seeing a position in the industry in which I can put into practice my knowledge and experience, ultimately benefiting the operations of the organisation that I work for.

Experience

FOREIGN SUPPORT MANAGER

AMETHYST HOTEL

2012 - 2013

WEB DESIGNER

UBİT TECHNOLOGY

2018 - 2019

Education

College 22

Primary / Highschool

Learning Hardware and Computer Science Russian Federation , Moscow

International Language School 4

Englis

International English School Russian Federation , Moscow

Sakarya University

2014-Present

2002-2012

2008-2012

Computer Engineering

Faculty of Computer and Information Sciences Turkey , Sakarya